I'm going to say this for the first time.
My real name is Joycelyn Trinidad.
I'll let you know
once the magazine publishes
your shoot and interview, Savana.
I mean, Joyce.
Via, thank you so much.
Do we have a problem, Via?
You tell me.
Is there something I need to worry about?
What did you do?
Who did you tell your real name to?
I only told one person, Mommy.
It's so convenient
that right after I tell you my real name,
Girl with Periwinkle Hair released her video
and even dragged my father into it.
My whole life is now out in the open.
I admired what you did.
I have no control over the minds of people
who give malice to what you confessed, okay?
I'm sorry, Via.
I just can't bear all the bashing.
Get out of my office.
Because of the recent issue about Savana,
we decided to remove her from Josh's movie.
Remove me from the project, but retain Joyce.
Joyce will stay in the film
if you return to Casa Fuerte.
Mom?
Don't tell me
you're going to confess something.
Huh?
What are we doing in an orphanage?
[Bahay Aruga]
Am I adopted?
Silly!
I was the one who gave birth to you.
What are we doing here, then?
You said you have a problem, right?
You should rest once in a while.
I come here once a week.
I cook for the kids.
Once you get inside
and see the smile on the kids' faces,
you'll forget all about your problems.
You might realize somehow,
that you need to apologize to Via.
- Oh...
- Good morning.
Hello, Sister.
This is my son, Liam.
Hi, Liam. Good morning.
Good morning, too.
Good morning, my dearies!
We're now here in Bahay Aruga orphanage!
I said this is for good publicity.
So here it is, my dearies!
We're here with the one and only, Savana.
Savana, please say hi to our viewers.
Good morning! Savana just woke up.
Smile!
Smile, girl! There.
Later, Savana and I will have a coffee date.
So, I'll also interview her
about her gifts for the kids
in Bahay Aruga.
Almost every week, we're here in...
Actually, the angle there is nicer.
- Let's go there.
- Okay. Let's see.
- Take your camera over there.
- Wait.
Savana.
I mean, Joyce.
Liam?
My dear, who's that?
He's good-looking.
He's the creative manager of her movie.
Creative manager?
Is he single?
Let's go over there. Let's work. Come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
Good morning.
Good morning, good morning.
We're so happy to be here.
So excited, my goodness.
Do you want to come back some other day, son?
No need.
We're here anyway.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Here.
- Here. Juice.
- Here.
- Juice.
- Get a fork over there.
Hi!
You can use this for your lesson, right?
I don't use a coloring book anymore.
Just take it.
Thank you.
Mommy...
Come on, smile.
Smile.
Hi! Here. Give it to her.
You're so beautiful.
The nuns and I have been
watching you in Captive Hearts.
Thank you. You're so pretty too.
- Hi, my dearies.
- Mommy...
Hurry up, come here. Come and get it.
- Here, here, here.
- There you go.
Baby, say hi. Say hi to my vlog.
Hi, my dearies!
Hi!
Mommy, let's stop.
I'm going to do this sincerely,
but not like this.
We're using the kids.
Come on, just smile. Smile!
Give it to her.
- Give it to her.
- Hi!
Hello.
That looks so nice.
Wait, I want to join you.
There, it's so beautiful.
Picture!
Picture? Okay, game, game, game.
One, two, three.
Hi! There you go. One more. The next one.
Baby, say hi to the camera.
I'll just refill this one.
Okay.
Joyce?
Can you help me here?
Okay.
Wait!
Here.
For you. Look at the camera.
Okay, next.
- Next.
My dear Aunt, what do we serve the kids?
Don't focus the camera on me.
I'm not a celebrity who needs attention.
Okay. I'll just focus on the food.
Yes.
Go ahead. Laugh.
What?
Laugh.
I know what I do for publicity
is so pathetic.
You know, ever since...
I started working with you...
I've learned a lot of things about showbiz.
So I won't be surprised by this.
I'm sorry if...
if I called you.
I just wanted to check on you.
Even though I knew you wanted to be alone.
My mom took my phone.
I'm still sorry for all the things
you're going through.
I'm used to it.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
I'm sure there will be a new rumor
that people will obsess about.
You probably heard about what I did to Via.
Liam, I want to...
I want to apologize to her,
but she won't answer my calls.
I want to be given a chance
to apologize to her in person.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to her.
Thank you.
Joyce, I also have something to confess...
about our movie.
The movie will push through...
because I made a deal with
my dad and Uncle Ramon.
What deal?
I don't have it.
You do! You took it!
- I said I don't have it.
- You do!
I don't have it.
You do! You took it!
- I said I don't have it.
- You do!
You took it from me!
- Give it back!
- I don't have it!
- Dex!
- You do!
- I don't have it!
Dex!
Dex! Kid.
Where's the kid you were chasing earlier?
He'll be dead meat once Bating catches him.
Liam?
Who are you looking for?
Don't worry about it.
I just thought I saw something.
Dex?
Dex.
You're dead meat, Daddy.
Mom is mad at you again.
That's how much your mom loves.
So, let's go?
My boy...
Who is Dex?
My name's Sep.
Sep, come here.
Give me my pencil back.
I said I don't have it.
Give it to me!
You have it. Give me my pencil back.
I said no. I don't have it.
Oops!
Hey, that's enough.
Fighting is not a good thing.
I will tell on you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm used to Bating.
They always pick on me.
Is that so?
Always be a good kid.
Hi, Sep.
Can I see
if you've tried anything
in your coloring book?
Come on, let's color.
Let me see.
Joyce... Dex.
My wife and son.
You've got a lot of rubber bands on your arm.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I used to like rubber bands too
when I was a kid.
And I used to like doing stars.
Do you know how to do it?
No.
Do you want me to teach you?
Let me have a rubber band.
Do this.
Put it down first.
You should hold it like this.
Insert it like this, then reach it here,
then turn it like this.
One more.
Reach for it, then turn it like this.
Place it here on your thumb.
Pull it out. Like that.
Can I see?
Let me see.
Liam, we've given all the kids their food.
Thank you, Mom.
Hello.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Not yet?
Here. Luckily, there's still one left.
Spaghetti.
Thank you.
Oh, dear.
You're so sweet.
You were like Liam when he was a kid.
You're so handsome.
Go eat.
Savana, let's go. We're done here.
Are you leaving too, Liam?
Auntie Tess?
Maybe we'll stay a little longer.
Why, son?
Savana, come on.
Bye.
Thank you.
I really didn't get Bating's pencil.
Don't indulge someone who is
picking a fight with you, okay?
Tell the nuns instead.
Yes, Miss Savana.
Promise.
Just call me Joyce.
Yes, Miss Joyce.
Liam, see you at Blacksmith.
Son, why are we staying?
Sep?
Where is the nun's office?
Over there.
[Bahay Aruga]
Can you draw a tree?
- Let me see.
- Later.
I will make a...
What are you drawing?
Is that me?
He is Sep.
Stefano Lualhati is his real name.
He came here just recently.
They said he is from Verde Village.
Based on our records, he's already orphaned.
Verde Village?
Why, Liam?
Do you know the kid's parents?
You're the reason we're suffering.
They're humans.
They are not flies you can shoo away
from their homes.
Even though you took the wrong path,
the heart will lead you to the right way.
No, Sister.
Sorry. I was shocked.
I thought he is here
because he got separated from his parents.
Turns out he's an orphan.
I'll go ahead.
Thank you so much, Sister.
No, it's my brother.
It's made out of his name.
Royce. R...
How was it, son?
Did you get what you needed?
Yes.
I was told that Sep was from Verde Village.
I want to talk to Mister Nestor.
He might know Sep.
The old man who almost killed...
Son, why would you go back there?
And why are you suddenly interested in Sep?
If he's from Verde Village
and already an orphan,
I want to know
if Casa Fuerte has to do
with the death of his parents.
Okay.
I'll come with you.
Hey.
You have a wound.
It's nothing.
I can even do TikTok.
Wow, TikTok.
Wow!
Gosh...
I better bring you to the clinic
before you do TikTok.
Thank you, Sir Liam. You're so kind.
How did you know my name?
I heard it from Miss Joyce.
She called you Liam.
You're like Miss Joyce.
You're both very kind.
I will wait for you to come back.
Promise, I'll come back.
But before that, I'll bring you to the clinic.
Come on, let's go. Oh, dear.
The orphanage was correct.
He's now an orphan.
What?
Why? What happened?
He's one reason
why the residents of the Village are furious
at Casa Fuerte.
His family moved to a riverside place
when they got evicted from their home.
His parents drowned
when the water swelled during a typhoon.
Sep was the only one who survived.
So even though we reconciled, Liam,
things like this will still remind us
how your company made us suffer.
He's Sep.
Stefano Lualhati is his real name.
He came here just recently.
They said he was from Verde Village.
And based on our records,
he's already an orphan.
I thought we came here to talk.
I'm sorry, Via.
Thank you so much for agreeing to talk.
I can't say no to you.
I heard from Dad
that you backed out of Blacksmith's movie.
I think it's a good idea
that you return to Casa Fuerte.
In that case, I won't be forced
to get involved in the movie, either.
I have already forgotten what Joyce did.
Via, I also invited Joyce tonight.
Please follow me, Sir, Ma'am.
Mr. Herrera and his companion
are already here.
Liam.
Good evening.
Via.
- Go on.
- I can adjust the table for you.
Yes, please. We know each other, anyway.
That's okay.
Come, Hans. Join us.
Should I?
Yeah.
Help me.
Let me help you.
- It's okay. We got this.
- Everything good now?
Okay.
It's a bit chilly, right?
Let's go.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
So, Liam, you're back from Bahay Aruga.
How was it?
Bahay Aruga?
Oh, yeah.
It's an orphanage.
Mom brought me with her
when she visited for the kids.
It was a coincidence
that Joyce was there, too.
Mom and I haven't gone back there yet.
By the way, Liam,
regarding Savana's action scenes,
please take care of her.
I mean, Joyce.
Sorry. I'm not used to calling you Joyce.
You were already using the name Savana
when I met you.
Liam here is so used to calling her Joyce.
It seems like
they've known each other for a long time.
- Actually, Via...
- Via, can we talk?
- Go ahead.
- You go first.
They both went silent.
Hans, just so you know,
Liam is no longer working for Blacksmith.
He can't keep an eye on Joyce anymore
during her action scenes.
Sorry, he's going to return to Casa Fuerte.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You resigned from Blacksmith?
What about our movie?
Well, I guess,
we've established
that my boyfriend has many secrets.
Via.
What?
I didn't know
you and Joyce met at the orphanage.
Joyce didn't know
that you're no longer in Blacksmith.
Excuse me. I'll just go to the powder room.
I'll use the restroom, too.
Joyce.
Is Via still mad at me?
Hans and I can leave.
It's okay. I'll tell him we're leaving.
Joyce, about my resignation at Blacksmith...
I tried to tell you
when we were at the orphanage.
But I lost the chance.
Did you follow me here to explain?
Joyce, I didn't want you
to find out this way.
Liam, I can't do anything...
if that's your decision.
And you don't have to explain.
What's taking them so long?
Maybe it's crowded.
Probably, there's a line.
You're the editor-in-chief
of Escale Magazine, right?
Yeah.
I know it's far different from Liam's job.
You're the human rights lawyer?
Yes.
And far different from Joyce's job too.
You know what they say.
Opposites attract. Right?
Yes, I agree.
That's why sometimes I cannot keep up
with the things she does.
I only watch her shows.
It was Liam
who taught me terms regarding heavy equipment.
To our opposites.
So without any pretensions...
I really wish for you
to be happy with your choice.
I have no choice, Joyce.
If there's something I learned
from making our movie...
it is...
We all have a choice.
You taught me how to be brave.
You taught me
to choose what I think is better for me.
I dared to be honest with myself...
But I went overboard.
That's why I did Via wrong.
I really want to talk to her.
I don't think Via will talk to you.
So she's still mad at me.
Joyce-
Don't blame yourself.
I have no one to blame but myself.
That is
what taking full accountability means, Liam.
And I think that's what you should also do...
Take full accountability
for all your decisions.
Joyce.
I'm sorry.
I better check on them.
- Are you going, too?
- Okay.
Go ahead.
Can I talk to you?
I want to apologize.
I want to apologize...
because I know I did you wrong.
You know what's funny?
Before you came,
I told Liam I wasn't ready yet to see you.
But Liam advised me...
to put myself in your shoes...
so I could understand why you did that.
And because I love Liam,
I'll heed his advice.
I'll understand.
Thank you, Via.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
There's just one thing I want clarified.
What is it?
Is something going on between you and Liam?
Are you having an affair with my boyfriend?
What?
No.
No. Nothing's going on between Liam and me.
When we were at your resort,
Liam got so drunk.
He called me Joyce.
Back then, I didn't know who Joyce was.
Then, I found out that you are Joyce.
Via, I don't know either.
Liam... Liam has known my real name
for a long time now.
College. We met during college.
We were classmates in college.
So you have a past.
We don't have a past.
Via, believe me, please.
I want to.
Oh my God.
Please, Via.
Are you mad?
Are you mad because of what I asked you?
No, I'm not...
It's okay if you're mad, Savana.
So you'll also know
how it feels to be wrongly accused.
I'm sorry.
I thought Joyce already knew
you were no longer in Blacksmith.
I want to go home.
Hey.
Is everything all right?
Want to go somewhere else?
I'll go with you.
Sorry, Hans, but I want to go home.
What happened?
Okay.
- I want to go home.
- Okay, okay.
Please.
I'll drive you home.
I'm having a hard time.
This is not the life I chose.
This is not me.
I want to go home!
Then go home. It's so simple.
Bro.
I wish it was that easy, Intoy.
Bro, there's a mountain of trash.
Everything is there...
Carton, plastic, bottle, diaper, poop.
Everything is there
because it's a mountain of trash.
And me? I'm underneath.
Why?
What do you mean "why"?
I was buried under the trash.
Sorry, I didn't know.
You're not listening.
I was buried under a mountain of trash.
Do you know what I told myself?
Ask me what I told myself.
What did you tell yourself?
I told myself...
"I will go home".
I did it, bro.
I forced myself out.
I climbed my way up to the top.
And when I got out, I took a deep breath.
It still smelled like trash.
It still smelled like poop.
I said, "I'm not going to die here".
I'll go home. But...
But to where?
Bro, wherever you think home is.
Sir Liam, do stars grow old?
Yes.
But it grows old very slowly.
They live for a long time?
Very long.
They live millions of years.
Wow, I wish I was a star.
Why?
So that I can spend millions of years
with my parents before they die.
Sep.
I wish we were all stars.
Even though we know we will lose someone,
we can still make the most of our time
with them.
Because we'll spend a long time with them.
That's what I said.
Do you have a problem, Sir Liam?
Yes.
When someone gets old, his problems pile up.
So sometimes, I wish I was a star.
My mom had so many problems, too.
My dad had heart disease,
but we didn't have money for his medicines.
So this is what I did.
He said he felt better.
He said his loved ones make him feel better.
Is the pain in your chest getting better,
Sir Liam?
It does get better.
So much.
I remember someone
who looks exactly like you.
Oh, so there's someone else
as good-looking as me.
Not just as handsome as you.
He's also as kind as you.
This is what we'll do, Edison.
Someone will walk by.
I want a continuous shot.
Here, here, here. Like this.
Are you ready, Josh?
Of course.
I was born ready. You know that.
- Dee? Dee?
- What happened?
- What happened to you?
- Hurry up! Call someone!
Hi, Director Phil!
Hi.
Megan sent me the script.
Congratulations. It's our first big day.
And it's a big scene!
This is an exciting day, right, Savana?
I should call you Joyce.
I have to get used to it.
Hi, Director Phil.
Who can perform first-aid?
Medic!
- Please help her!
- Let me do it.
- Medic!
- Deedee!
- Medic?
- Okay, okay, wait.
I got this.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
This girl loves eating. That's why.
My gosh, Dee.
Sorry.
Thank you.
But that's impressive.
You're great.
Very good.
By the way, this is Sep.
Liam and I met him at the orphanage.
He asked us to bring him here to the set.
We asked for permission from the nuns.
And luckily, they allowed us.
Promise, Director. I'll behave.
I just want to watch the filming.
Really? When I say "Quiet on the set",
you stay quiet, okay?
Promise, Director Phil.
Promise?
I can't let you do this.
I love him, Dad.
- Via!
- Spoiled brat!
What do you know about love?
Dad, please. No, no, no, please!
No! Don't! Not Liam, please.
I love him!
Stop!
You're being like that...
You think about nothing but power and money,
because you lost Mom, right?
Don't drag your mom into this.
I wish I had gone with Mom.
That only changed because of Liam.
So if you want to take him away from me, go.
Go ahead. Kill me first.
Medic!